# **Sharde Wormley**

#### People-oriented outstanding communication skills

Fort Worth, TX shardewormley85@gmail.com 682-459-6611

I'm a very caring and compassionate person that's why I became a Certified nurse aide, I also have great communication skills. I've been a certified nursing assistant 5 years i love what i do, doing this brings me joy knowing i help people.. I also have experience with dementia patients, and helping with Hospice patients. My biggest strength is giving my all to my job, doing my best to satisfy everyone and always remembering that the customers are number one. I have warehouse experience, I've done cell phone work, order pulling and shipping and receiving, material handling. I'm a fast learner and always willing to learn new things.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### **Certified Nursing Assistant**

Williamsburg Village Healthcare - DeSoto, TX March 2019 to Present

Assisting patients with activities of daily living. Customer service, documentation. Training in Alzheimer's and Dementia

#### Multi Skilled Tech/Cna

Texas Health Huguley Hospital - Burleson, TX January 2018 to September 2018

PCU unit. Putting leads on patients, setting room up for new admits, vital signs every 4 hours, blood sugars. Documentation on patients, standard precautions on isolation patients.

#### **Certified Nursing Assistant**

Stonegate Nursing Center - Fort Worth, TX December 2015 to March 2017

Assisting with activities of daily living, charting, answering call lights, vital signs, transferring patients, assisting nurse with wound care

#### Cell Phone Technician, production worker

NewBreed Logistics(adecco temp) - Fort Worth, TX July 2012 to April 2013

Inspector of iPhones, production and assembly line of products, scanning products in computer systems, order pulling

### Education

### **Diploma**

#### Fort Worth can academy

#### Skills

experienced in Hospice care and working with Alzheimer's and dementia patients, long term care, assisted living and memory care experiece (5 years), Warehouse work,order pulling, shipping and receiving (1 year), Vital signs, assisting nurse with wound care, catheter care (5 years), CNA, Cna Certified

# Certifications/Licenses

### certified nurse assistant

April 2013

Nurse aide training CPR certification

## **Certified Nursing Assistant (CNA)**

## Additional Information

I have cell phone experience, Inspecting Iphones, data r, cosmetics checks on cellphones, Qc experience, material handling.